

DO KHANH DAT

CHEMICAL TECHNICIAN

CONTACT

- **1** 058-246-1618
- dokhanhdat2605@gmail.com
- HT23 Street, Hiep Thanh Ward,District 12, Ho Chi Minh City

EDUCATION

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology and Education

2020-2024

Chemical Engineering Major: Organic Chemistry

GPA: 8.00/10

SKILLS

- Performing modern analysis
- Data processing and evaluation
- Laboratory techniques and procedures
- Teamwork
- Proficient user of MS software such as Word, Excel, and
 PowerPoint

PROFILE

I have just successfully defended my graduation thesis at HCMC University of Technology and Education. Throughout my four years at university, I've been a fast learner and have gained some essential engineering and quality control skills such as critical thinking, problem-solving, and teamwork. I'm very excited about new opportunities and challenges where I can learn about laboratory skills. I believe that the knowledge and experience I have gained will contribute to the success of the company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

R&D Intern

07/2023 - 09/2023

LIX DETERGENT JOINT STOCK COMPANY

- Assisted in conducting laboratory experiments, including sample preparation, product quality testing, and recording results.
- Contributed ideas to the new product development process.
- Exposed to and worked with modern analytical equipment in the laboratory.
- Accumulated experience in teamwork and effective communication in a dynamic work environment.

Student Research

10/2023 - now

HCMC University of Technology and Education

- Conducted research in "Fluorescence quenching kinetics of α -glucosidase by novel 2,3-dihydroxychalconoids".
- Exposed to and operated modern equipment such as preparative HPLC, UV-Vis, PL, and Elisa Microplate Reader.

CERTIFICATES

- English Skill (TOEIC 535).
- Completed the course: IELTS INTERMEDIATE (BAND 6.0 - 6.5) at English House Center.
- Completed the courses of 2022 Holiday School -Introduction to Biomedical Mechanics.
- Participated in the 2023 International Summer School organized within the frame of the EU-funded project "Future-ORiented chEmiSTry, FOREST".

ACTIVITIES

- Advisor for the Freshmen Mentoring Program, supporting the school's recruitment efforts.
- Served as an outstanding Youth Union Secretary for four consecutive years.